Some fight to win. He fought to live.
The Survivor is a history, action, drama film directed by Barry Levinson.
Harry Haft is a boxer who fought fellow prisoners in
the concentration camps to survive.
Haunted by the memories and his guilt, he attempts to use high-profile fights against
boxing legends like Rocky Marciano as a way to find his first love again.
Harry Haft, played by Ben Foster.
Schneider, played by Billy Magnussen.
Miriam Wofsoniker, played by Vicky Krieps.
Emory Anderson, played by Peter Sarsgaard.
Peretz Haft, played by Saro Emirze.
Charley Goldman, played by Danny DeVito.
The Survivor is a 2021 biographical drama film directed by Barry
Levinson from a screenplay by Justine Juel Gillmer.
Ben Foster stars as Harry Haft, a real-life survivor of the Nazi Germany
Auschwitz concentration camp, where he boxed fellow inmates to survive.
Vicky Krieps, Billy Magnussen, Peter Sarsgaard, John
Leguizamo, and Danny DeVito co-star.
The film had its world premiere at the Toronto International Film Festival in
September 2021, and was released on HBO on April 27, 2022.
The film received positive reviews from critics,
particularly for Foster's lead performance.
The film was Emmy nominated for Outstanding Television Movie.
The film explores themes of concentration camp, world war ii,
boxer, trauma, concentration camp survivor.
The tone is emotional.